A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 3, Series 15 FA1485
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants and Program Files, 1982-2012; 1
  - American Institutes for Research - Moon (20030513) - Proposal Development (Box 313, Folder 8)
  - American Institutes for Research - Moon (20030513) - Correspondence (Box 314, Folder 1)
  - American Institutes for Research - Moon (20030513) - Grant Products (Box 314, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, School of Law - Sage (20050320), 2005-2008 (Box 314, Folder 3)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Chiplin (20070487), 2007-2008 (Box 314, Folder 4)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Chiplin (20070487) - Proposal Development (Box 314, Folder 5)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Chiplin (20070487) - Articles and Background (Box 314, Folder 6)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Chiplin (20070487) - Budget and Administration (Box 314, Folder 7)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Chiplin (20070487) - Correspondence (Box 314, Folder 8)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Chiplin (20070487) - Grant Products (Box 314, Folder 9)
  - National Council on the Aging - Firman (20040464), 2004-2005 (Box 315, Folder 1)
  - National Council on the Aging - Firman (20040464) - Grant Products (Box 315, Folder 2)
  - National Council on the Aging - Firman (20040464) - Proposal Development (Box 315, Folder 3)
  - National Council on the Aging - Firman (20040464) - Budget and Administration (Box 315, Folder 4)
  - National Council on the Aging - Firman (20040464) - Grant Products (Box 315, Folder 5)
  - Children's Defense Fund - Lawrence (20020075), 2001-2004 (Box 315, Folder 6-7)
  - Children's Defense Fund - Lawrence (20020075) - Grant Products (Box 316, Folder 1-2)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Anderson (20070117), 2006-2007 (Box 316, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Jewish Health System - Fishman (20050197), 2004-2008 (Box 316, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Jewish Health System - Fishman (20050197) - Grant Products (Box 317, Folder 1)
  - RAND Corporation - Saliba (20031442), 2003-2004 (Box 317, Folder 2)
  - National Opinion Research Center - Whitmore and Gabel (20050642), 2005-2007 (Box 317, Folder 3-4)
  - National Opinion Research Center - Whitmore and Gabel (20050642) - Grant Products (Box 317, Folder 5)
  - National Opinion Research Center - Whitmore and Gabel (20050642) - Grant Products (Box 318, Folder 1-2)
  - University of Wisconsin - Zimmerman (20020672) - Grant Products (Box 318, Folder 3)
  - University of Wisconsin - Zimmerman (20020672) - Articles and Background (Box 318, Folder 4)
  - University of Wisconsin - Zimmerman (20020672) - Budget and Administration (Box 318, Folder 5)
  - University of Wisconsin - Zimmerman (20020672) - Correspondence (Box 318, Folder 6)
  - University of Wisconsin - Zimmerman (20020672) - Proposal Development (Box 318, Folder 7)
  - Brandeis University - Gittell (20020185), 2002-2006 (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Brandeis University - Gittell (20020185) - Grant Products (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Brandeis University - Gittell (20020185) - Correspondence (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - Brandeis University - Bishop (990136) - Draft Papers (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - AcademyHealth - Pittman (20040806), 2004-2006 (Box 320, Folder 1-2)
  - National Senior Citizen's Law Center - Semmel (20010724) - Pace Programs and Alternatives to Facilitate Independent Living, 2001-2005 (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - National Senior Citizen's Law Center - Semmel (20010724) - Pace Programs and Alternatives to Facilitate Independent Living - Grant Products (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - National Senior Citizen's Law Center - Semmel (20010724) - Pace Programs and Alternatives to Facilitate Independent Living, 2001-2005 (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - Health Research, Inc. - Salsberg (20030586), 2003-2004 (Box 321, Folder 2-3)
  - National Governor's Association - Braunstein (20040172), 2004-2005 (Box 321, Folder 4)
  - Urban Institute - Berenson (20040492), 2004-2006 (Box 321, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Care Research Institute - Clark (20050053), 2004-2005 (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - Emergency Care Research Institute - Clark (20050053) - Proposal Development (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Emergency Care Research Institute - Clark (20050053) - Correspondence (Box 322, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Care Research Institute - Clark (20050053) - Budget and Administration (Box 322, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University - Kaplan (Box 322, Folder 5)
  - Pioneeer Network - Fagan (20030619), 2001-2004 (Box 322, Folder 6)
  - State of Washington, Department of Social and Health Services - Porter (20020590), 2002-2003 (Box 322, Folder 7)
  - State of Washington, Department of Social and Health Services - Porter (20020590) - Grant Products (Box 323, Folder 1)
  - State of Washington, Department of Social and Health Services - Porter (20020590) - Correspondence (Box 323, Folder 2)
  - State of Washington, Department of Social and Health Services - Porter (20020590) - Administration and Budget (Box 323, Folder 3)
  - State of Washington, Department of Social and Health Services - Porter (20020590) - Proposal Development (Box 323, Folder 4)
  - American Health Quality Association - Deutsch (20040491) (Box 323, Folder 5)
  - American Association of Nurse Assessment Coordinators - Carter (20040490) (Box 323, Folder 6)
  - The Margaret Blenkner Research Institute of Benjamin Rose - Ejaz (20020802), 2002-2005 (Box 323, Folder 7)
  - The Margaret Blenkner Research Institute of Benjamin Rose - Ejaz (20020802) - Articles and Background (Box 324, Folder 1)
  - The Margaret Blenkner Research Institute of Benjamin Rose - Ejaz (20020802) - Grant Products (Box 324, Folder 2-3)
  - The Margaret Blenkner Research Institute of Benjamin Rose - Ejaz (20020802) - Correspondence (Box 324, Folder 4)
  - The Margaret Blenkner Research Institute of Benjamin Rose - Ejaz (20020802) - Administration and Budget (Box 324, Folder 5)
  - The Margaret Blenkner Research Institute of Benjamin Rose - Ejaz (20020802) - Proposal Development (Box 325, Folder 1)
  - Grantmakers in Aging - Farquhar (20040528) - Grant Products (Box 325, Folder 2)
  - Grantmakers in Aging - Farquhar (20040528) - Correspondence (Box 325, Folder 3)
  - Grantmakers in Aging - Farquhar (20040528) - Proposal Development (Box 325, Folder 4)
  - Delmarva Foundation for Medical Care, Inc. - Paganelli (20020708) (Box 325, Folder 5)
  - NASHP - Riley (990423) - Grant Products, 2000 (Box 325, Folder 6)
  - FACCT - Bethell (980495), 1999 (Box 325, Folder 7)
  - Yale University - Inouye (20020119) - Tools and Disemination of Help - Grant Products (Box 325, Folder 8)
  - AcademyHealth - Child Health Services Research (CHSR) Annual Meeting (20040494) (Box 325, Folder 9)
  - NICHQ (20020386) (Box 326, Folder 1-2)
  - FACCT - Bethell (980498), 1998-1999 (Box 326, Folder 3-4)
  - Yale University, School of Nursing - Crowley (20010134) - Integrating Healthy Steps into Graduate Pediatric Nursing, 2000-2001 (Box 327, Folder 1)
  - Yale University, School of Nursing - Crowley (20010134) - Integrating Healthy Steps into Graduate Pediatric Nursing - Grant Products (Box 327, Folder 2-3)
  - Yale University, School of Nursing - Crowley (20010134) - Integrating Healthy Steps into Graduate Pediatric Nursing - Proposal (Box 327, Folder 4)
  - Yale University, School of Nursing - Crowley (20010134) - Integrating Healthy Steps into Graduate Pediatric Nursing - Administration and Budget (Box 327, Folder 5)
  - Yale University, School of Nursing - Crowley (20010134) - Integrating Healthy Steps into Graduate Pediatric Nursing - Correspondence (Box 327, Folder 6)
  - Yale University, School of Nursing - Crowley (20010134) - Integrating Healthy Steps into Graduate Pediatric Nursing - Yale Concept Paper (Box 327, Folder 7)
  - Yale University, School of Nursing - Crowley (20010134) - Integrating Healthy Steps into Graduate Pediatric Nursing (Box 327, Folder 8)
  - Georgetown University - Cooper (20031424), 2003-2005 (Box 327, Folder 9)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute - Silow-Carroll (20031272), 2003-2004 (Box 328, Folder 1)
  - Project Hope Center for Health Affairs - Schur (20020847) (Box 328, Folder 2)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals - Safran (20010442) (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - The National Council on Aging - Whitelaw (20020175), 2001-2002 (Box 328, Folder 4)
  - Rutgers University - Fox (20040702), 2004-2005 (Box 328, Folder 5)
  - Georgetown University - Cooper (20040721) - Program Direction - Program on Medicare's Future, 2004-2005 (Box 328, Folder 6)
  - National Senior Citizens Law Center - Kelly (20070488), 2007-2008 (Box 328, Folder 7)
  - National Senior Citizens Law Center - Kelly (20070488) - Grant Products (Box 328, Folder 8)
  - National Senior Citizens Law Center - Kelly (20070488) - Proposal Development (Box 329, Folder 1)
  - National Senior Citizens Law Center - Kelly (20070488) - Articles and Background (Box 329, Folder 2)
  - National Senior Citizens Law Center - Kelly (20070488) - Budget and Administration (Box 329, Folder 3)
  - National Senior Citizens Law Center - Kelly (20070488) - Grant Products - Correspondence (Box 329, Folder 4)
  - Georgetown University - Summer (20060282), 2006-2008 (Box 329, Folder 5)
  - Georgetown University - Summer (20060282) - Proposal Development (Box 329, Folder 6)
  - Georgetown University - Summer (20060282) - Budget and Administration (Box 329, Folder 7)
  - Georgetown University - Summer (20060282) - Correspondence (Box 329, Folder 8)
  - Georgetown University - Summer (20060282) - Grant Products (Box 329, Folder 9-10)
  - University of Texas, Austin - Apfel (20031434), 2003-2006 (Box 329, Folder 11)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals - Safran (20020740), 2002-2008 (Box 330, Folder 1)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals - Safran (20020740) - Surveys of Prescription Drug Coverage - Survey Development (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals - Safran (20020740) - Surveys of Prescription Drug Coverage - Survey Data Year 2 (Box 330, Folder 3)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals - Safran (20020740) - Surveys of Prescription Drug Coverage - Final Surveys - Year 2 (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals - Safran (20020740) - Surveys of Prescription Drug Coverage - Grant Products (Box 330, Folder 5)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals - Safran (20020740) - Surveys of Prescription Drug Coverage - Correspondence (Box 330, Folder 6)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals - Safran (20020740) - Surveys of Prescription Drug Coverage - Products - Year 2 (Box 330, Folder 7)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals - Safran (20020740) - Surveys of Prescription Drug Coverage - Budget and Administration (Box 331, Folder 1-2)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals - Safran (20020740) - Surveys of Prescription Drug Coverage - Articles and Background (Box 331, Folder 3)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals - Safran (20020740) - Surveys of Prescription Drug Coverage - Grant Products (Box 331, Folder 4)
  - The Urban Institute - Berenson (20040457), 2004-2006 (Box 331, Folder 5)
  - The Urban Institute - Berenson (20040457) - Grant Products (Box 331, Folder 6)
  - The Urban Institute - Berenson (20040457) - Proposal Development (Box 331, Folder 7)
  - The Urban Institute - Berenson (20040457) - Budget and Administration (Box 331, Folder 8)
  - The Urban Institute - Berenson (20040457) - Correspondence (Box 331, Folder 9)
  - Research Foundation of the State University of New York (SUNY) - Saleh (20060361) (Box 331, Folder 10)
  - Research Foundation of the State University of New York (SUNY) - Saleh (20060361) - Grant Products (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Chiplin (20060457), 2006-2007 (Box 332, Folder 2)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Chiplin (20060457) - Budget and Administration (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Chiplin (20060457) - Proposal Development (Box 332, Folder 4)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Chiplin (20060457) - Grant Products (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Milligan (20070150), 2006-2008 (Box 332, Folder 6)
  - University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Milligan (20070150) - Budget and Administration (Box 333, Folder 1)
  - University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Milligan (20070150) - Proposal Development (Box 333, Folder 2)
  - University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Milligan (20070150) - Correspondence (Box 333, Folder 3)
  - University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Milligan (20070150) - Grant Products (Box 333, Folder 4)
  - University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Milligan (20070652), 2007-2008 (Box 333, Folder 5)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York - Haslanger (20050094), 2004-2007 (Box 333, Folder 6-8)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York - Haslanger (20050094) (Box 334, Folder 1)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York - Haslanger (20050094) - Grant Products (Box 334, Folder 2)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York - Haslanger (20050094) - Proposal Development (Box 334, Folder 3)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York - Haslanger (20050094) - Budget and Administration (Box 334, Folder 4)
  - United Methodist Senior Services of Mississippi - McAlilly (20060145), 2005 (Box 334, Folder 5)
  - Yale University - Bourbonniere (20070025), 2006-2007 (Box 334, Folder 6)
  - Greater New York Hospital Foundation - Johnson (20040573), 2004-2006 (Box 334, Folder 7)
  - The Lewin Group - Chimento (20020438) - Developing an Electronic Application for New York's Public Insurance Programs, 2002-2007 (Box 334, Folder 8)
  - The Lewin Group - Chimento (20020438) - Developing an Electronic Application for New York's Public Insurance Programs - Grant Products (Box 335, Folder 1)
  - The Lewin Group - Chimento (20020438) - Developing an Electronic Application for New York's Public Insurance Programs - Correspondence (Box 335, Folder 2)
  - The Lewin Group - Chimento (20020438) - Developing an Electronic Application for New York's Public Insurance Programs - Administration and Budget (Box 335, Folder 3)
  - The Lewin Group - Chimento (20020438) - Developing an Electronic Application for New York's Public Insurance Programs - Articles and Background (Box 335, Folder 4)
  - The Lewin Group - Chimento (20020438) - Developing an Electronic Application for New York's Public Insurance Programs - Proposal Development (Box 335, Folder 5)
  - Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20050089), 2004-2007 (Box 335, Folder 6)
  - Georgetown University - Freidland (20000450), 2000-2002 (Box 335, Folder 7)
  - Take the Field - Musca (20010531), 2001-2004 (Box 335, Folder 8)
  - Health Research and Educational Trust - Gabel (20030127), 2002-2007 (Box 336, Folder 1)
  - United Hospital Fund - Tallon (20070752) (Box 336, Folder 2)
  - Greater New York Hospital Association - Johnson (20070482) (Box 336, Folder 3)
  - Academy for Educational Development - Shimmyo (20070246) (Box 336, Folder 4)
  - National Medical Fellowships - Dyer (20080153) (Box 336, Folder 5)
  - Womens Prison Association and Home - Jacobs (20070540) (Box 336, Folder 6)
  - Primary Care Development Corp. - Kotelchuck (20070438) (Box 336, Folder 7)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Boufford (20070294) (Box 336, Folder 8)
  - National Medical Fellowships - 2007 Tenth Annual Gala - Dyer (20070293) (Box 336, Folder 9)
  - The Urban Institute - Moon (990204), 1998-2001 (Box 336, Folder 10)
  - MedStat - Marder (20040288) (Box 336, Folder 11)
  - Center for Budget and Policy Priorities - Ku (20030375), 2003-2004 (Box 336, Folder 12)
  - Medicare Rights Center, Inc. - Hayes (20030374), 2003-2005 (Box 336, Folder 13)
  - Medicare Rights Center, Inc. - Hayes (20030374) - Grant Products (Box 337, Folder 1)
  - Mathematica Policy Research - Gold (20010685), 2001-2003 (Box 337, Folder 2)
  - Georgetown University - Freidland (20020499), 2002-2006 (Box 337, Folder 3)
  - Georgetown University - Freidland (20020499) - Grant Products (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - The National Council on the Aging - Firman (20010613), 2001-2003 (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - The National Council on the Aging - Firman (20030093), 2002-2004 (Box 337, Folder 6)
  - Arc of the United States - Claypool (20040238), 2003-2005 (Box 338, Folder 1)
  - Arc of the United States - Claypool (20040238) - Grant Products (Box 338, Folder 2)
  - Arc of the United States - Claypool (20040238) - Interviews (Box 338, Folder 3)
  - Avalere Health, LLC - Carino (20060211), 2005-2007 (Box 338, Folder 4)
  - National Opinion Research Center (NORC) - Gabel (20020690) (Box 345, Folder 5)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Task Force Media Coverage, 1999-2003 (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Website Development Meetings, 2001-2003 (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Insurance Purchasers Meeting, 2000 December (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Fall Meeting 2000, 2000 October (Box 346, Folder 3)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Fall Meeting 2000, 2000 December (Box 346, Folder 4)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Spring Meeting 2001, 2001 March (Box 346, Folder 5)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Spring Meeting 2001, 2001 March (Box 347, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Fall Meeting 2001, 2001 October (Box 347, Folder 2)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Grantee and Colleague Meeting 2001, 2001 September (Box 347, Folder 3)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Spring Meeting 2002, 2002 March (Box 347, Folder 4)
  - 2020 Vision Policy Fellows Meeting, 2002 May (Box 347, Folder 5)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Grantee and Colleague Meeting 2002, 2002 September (Box 347, Folder 6)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Fall Meeting 2002, 2002 October (Box 348, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Spring Meeting 2003, 2003 March-April (Box 348, Folder 2-3)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Fall Meeting 2003, 2003 November (Box 348, Folder 4)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Fall Meeting 2004, 2004 October (Box 348, Folder 5)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Spring and Fall Meeting 2004 (Box 349, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Spring Meeting 2005, 2005 March (Box 349, Folder 2)
  - Princeton Survey Research Associates International - McIntosh (20030143) (Box 349, Folder 3)
  - Princeton Survey Research Associates - Colasanto (980775) - Low Income Workers Survey - RFP and Notes (Box 349, Folder 4)
  - State Innovations Program Proposal (Background), 2005 (Box 349, Folder 5)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Program Plan 2000-2001 (Box 349, Folder 6)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Program Plan 2001 (Box 350, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Program Plan 2002 (Box 350, Folder 2)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Program Expenses and Payments FY 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 350, Folder 3)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Program Expenses and Payments FY 2002, 2001-2002 (Box 350, Folder 4)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Program Expenses and Payments FY 2003, 2002-2003 (Box 350, Folder 5)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Program Expenses and Payments FY 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 350, Folder 6)
  - Program Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 350, Folder 7)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - General (Box 350, Folder 8)
  - Health Care Coverage and Quality Program - Advisory Committee Meeting, 1995 October 20 (Box 351, Folder 1)
  - Health Care Coverage, Access and Quality Program - Advisory Committee Meeting, 1996 May 2 (Box 351, Folder 2)
  - Health Care Coverage, Access and Quality Program - Advisory Committee Meeting, 1997 May 8 (Box 351, Folder 3)
  - Health Care Coverage, Access and Quality Program - Advisory Committee Meeting, 1997 December 8 (Box 351, Folder 4)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - First Meeting, 1999 October (Box 351, Folder 5)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Task Force Grant Tracking, Spring Meeting 2003, 2003 March-April (Box 352, Folder 1)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation - RAND (20050172), 2005-2009 (Box 352, Folder 2)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation - RAND (20050172) - Proposal Development (Box 352, Folder 3)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation - RAND (20050172) - Grant Products (Box 352, Folder 4)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation - RAND (20050172) - Proposal Development (Box 352, Folder 5)
  - 1996 Survey on Coverage and Access to Care - Taylor (96608) - Correspondence (Box 352, Folder 6)
  - 1996 Survey on Coverage and Access to Care - Taylor (96608) - Proposal Development (Box 352, Folder 7)
  - 1996 Survey on Coverage and Access to Care - Taylor (96608) - Grant Products (Box 352, Folder 8)
  - 1996 Survey on Coverage and Access to Care - Taylor (96608) - Articles and Background (Box 353, Folder 1)
  - 1996 Survey on Coverage and Access to Care - Taylor (96608) - Administration and Budget (Box 353, Folder 2)
  - 1996 Survey on Coverage and Access to Care - Taylor (96608) - Survey Development (Box 353, Folder 3-5)
  - New York University (NYU) - Billings (20000480) - Proposal Development (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - New York University (NYU) - Billings (20000480) - Meeting, 2003 December 16 (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - New York University (NYU) - Billings (20000480) - Correspondence (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - New York University (NYU) - Billings (20000480) - Articles and Background (Box 354, Folder 4)
  - New York University (NYU) - Billings (20000480) - Grant Products (Box 354, Folder 5)
  - New York University (NYU) - Billings (20000480) - Administration and Budget (Box 354, Folder 6)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Schoen (20020197) - Analytical Papers (Box 354, Folder 7)
  - Health Research and Educational Trust - Gabel (20000260), 1999-2001 (Box 354, Folder 8)
  - Alliance for Aging Research - Perry (20000698) - Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars, 2000-2001 (Box 355, Folder 1)
  - Alliance for Aging Research - Perry (20000698) - Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars, 2002-2003 (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - The Urban Institute - Moon (20020455) - Program on Medicare's Future, Year 7, 2002-2005 (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20070530) - Health Policy Seminars and Congressional Staff Retreat, 2007-2009 (Box 355, Folder 4-5)
  - Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20070530) - Health Policy Seminars and Congressional Staff Retreat, 2007-2008 (Box 356, Folder 1-3)
  - Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20070530) - Health Policy Seminars and Congressional Staff Retreat, 2008 (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20070529) - Commonwealth Fund Bipartisan Congressional Retreat 2008, 2007-2009 (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20070529) - Commonwealth Fund Bipartisan Congressional Retreat 2008 - Meeting (Box 357, Folder 3)
  - Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20070529) - Commonwealth Fund Bipartisan Congressional Retreat 2008 - Grant Products (Box 357, Folder 4)
  - Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20070529) - Commonwealth Fund Bipartisan Congressional Retreat 2008 - Grant Products (Box 358, Folder 1)
  - Penn State University - Short (20020516) - Filling Gaps in Health Insurance Over Time, 2003-2004 (Box 358, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University - Glied (20050084), 2003-2008 (Box 358, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University - Glied (20060135), 2005-2007 (Box 358, Folder 4)
  - Grantmakers in Aging - Farquhar (20060489), 2006-2007 (Box 358, Folder 5)
  - Grantmakers in Aging - Farquhar (20070357) (Box 358, Folder 6)